The lucky ones die first.
The Hills Have Eyes is a horror, thriller film directed by Alexandre Aja.
Based on Wes Craven's 1977 suspenseful cult classic, The Hills Have Eyes is the story of a family road trip
that goes terrifyingly awry when the travelers become stranded in a government atomic zone.
Miles from nowhere, the Carter family soon realizes the seemingly uninhabited wasteland is
actually the breeding ground of a blood-thirsty mutant family...and they are the prey.
Lynn, played by Vinessa Shaw.
Doug, played by Aaron Stanford.
Big Bob, played by Ted Levine.
Ethel, played by Kathleen Quinlan.
Brenda, played by Emilie de Ravin.
Bobby, played by Dan Byrd.
The Hills Have Eyes is a 2006 American horror film directed by Alexandre Aja and
co-written by Aja and Grégory Levasseur, in their English-language debut.
It is a remake of Wes Craven's 1977 film of the same name.
The film stars Aaron Stanford, Kathleen Quinlan, Vinessa Shaw, Emilie de Ravin, Dan Byrd, Robert Joy, and Ted Levine, and
follows a family that is targeted by a group of cannibalistic mutants after their car breaks down in the desert.
The Hills Have Eyes was released theatrically in the United
States and United Kingdom on March 10, 2006.
It earned $15.5 million in its opening weekend in the United States, where it was originally rated
NC-17 for strong, gruesome violence, but was later edited down to achieve an R rating.
An unrated DVD version was released on June 20, 2006.
A sequel, The Hills Have Eyes 2, was released in 2007.
The film explores themes of van, rape, ambush, gas station, new mexico.
The tone is dark and intense.